<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Psychometric</string>
    <string name="scenatio_title">Scenario 1:</string>
    <string name="situation_title">Situation 1:</string>
    <string name="answers_title">Answers 1:</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Psychometric Test</string>


    <string name="scenario_text">
        You are a Retail Assistant working in the Saldringham branch of More Then Pens plc, a national stationer\'s chain. More Than Pens has over 1000 stores, primarily in the UK, including 451 travels outlets at airports, train stations and motorway service areas and 627 high street stores.
        
        More Than Pens sells a wide range of newspapers, magazines, books, stationry and impulse products; most branches are open 7 days a week between 8.30am and 5.30pm.
        
        As a Retail Assistant you are responsible for providing exceptional costumer service whilst demonstrating product knowledge to maximise sales. You work primarily in the book section of the Saldringham branch, however all the branch staff work as a unified team and therefore you are often required to work in other sections throught the store.
    </string>


    <string name="situation_text">
        A costumer ha been browsing in your section for about 10 minutes and is looking incerasingly dissatisfied and flustrated. He approaches you and askswhether you have a particular book that he is looking for, and after checking on your computer, you have to inform him that it is currently \'out of stock\'.
        
        Review the following responses A to D and indicate which one you belive to be the response to the situation you would be \'most likely to make\' and the response to the situaton which you would be \'least likely to make\'.
    </string>

    <string-array name="answer_texts">
        <item>A) Apologise that the book is unavailable and suggest he try Morethanpens.co.uk or another online retailer instead.</item>
        <item>B) Offer to order the book for the customer and let him know how long this will take. Offer to all him when the book arrives.</item>
        <item>C) Give the customer the ISBN (book serial number) of the book so that he can easily and quickly search it out elsewhere, either online or at another bookshop.</item>
        <item>D) Suggest he try the Alpston branch of More Than Pens (which is the nearest neighbouring town, 40 minutes drive away) or other bookshops in Saldringham. </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="answer_result_texts">
        <item>A - (This is the least effective response as you are not giving the customer any direct help and you are unaware as to whether the customer has access to a computer and is able to shop \'online\'.)</item>
        <item>B - (This is the most effective response as you are trying to give the customer what he wants without him having to do too much more. By telling the customer how long it will take to order, he can make an informed decision as to whether he wishes to take this option).</item>
        <item>C – (A reasonable response but you are doing little to directly help the customer find the book; he will still have to make quite an effort himself.)</item>
        <item>D – (Not a particularly appropriate response as it is, almost certainly, obvious to the customer that he could try elsewhere and so your response is not adding any value to what he already knows. You have managed to make him aware of an alternative branch of More Than Pens, which is positiv, but perhaps you could have offered to ring that branch to check the availability of the book before the customer set off to Alpston. You could also have improved this response by giving the customer specific details of other local bookshops and how to find them as well as the address of the Alpston More Than pens branch.)</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
